

## CONTACT

- **\** 015750738432
- 85570 Markt Schwaben

## **EXPERTISE**

- Sales and Retail
- Social Media Marketing
- Innovative Graphic Solutions
- Content Management

## SOFTWARE

- HTML, CSS, Basics of JavaScript
- Trello Project Management
- Microsoft Office Apps (Word, Excel, PowerPoint & Publisher)
- Google Apps (Docs, Sheets & Drive)
- WEB Building Apps (WIX, Shopify & WordPress)
- Design & Editing Apps
   (Autodesk Sketchbook,
   Infinite Painter, Ibis Painter &
   Canva)

# **LANGUAGES**

- Macedonian (Native)
- English (IELTS Level C1)
- Serbian/Croatian (Level C1)

# **TINA ATANASOVA**

Creative and motivated professional with exceptional skills in planning, analytical thinking and executing strategies. A proven expert in successfully managing ad projects from concept to completion in the leisure, business travel and tourism industry. Adaptive personality with an ability to work with a team or independently, creating effectiveness and developing opportunities that further deliver the desired results.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### SHIPPING COORDINATOR

11.2021 - 10.2022

Mytheresa

• Quality control of luxury items

#### TRAVEL SPECIALIST

09.2018 - 03.2021

Golden Tour

- Managed hotel and air ticket reservations
- Direct and indirect sales and invoicing
- Created designs and new concepts for product promotions
- Managed marketing campaigns (newsletters, posts, ads)
- Built and updated company's website

### TRAVEL CONSULTANT

11.2009 - 08.2018

BTI Macedonia

- Managed hotel and rail reservations
- Organized meetings, incentives, conferences and events
- Direct and indirect sales and invoicing
- Did graphics for promotional materials

# **EDUCATION**

#### CAREER FOUNDRY

12.2022 - Present

Full Stack Web Development

- Frontend Development (HTML & CSS)
- Full-Stack Immersion in progress (Mongo, Express, React, Node)

#### SEE UNIVERSITY Tetovo

2004 - 2009

• Bachelor's Degree in English Language and Literature

# **CERTIFICATES**

- Intro to Frontend Development
- Galileo Selling Platform
- Amadeus Selling Platform
- IATA (International Air Transport Association)